## Mehdi Beddiaf

Software engineer

Informations

H1B visa

mehdi.beddiaf@gmail.com

https://www.mehdi-beddiaf.com

https://www.linkedin.com/in/mehdibeddiaf/

## Summary

Energetic software engineer with 2+ years experience developing robust code for high-volume businesses. Migrated some core legacy applications of ThredUp operations running in 4 distribution centers. An enthusiastic team player with a constant need of intellectual stimulation.

## Experience

2016 - 2018 Software Engineer @ Fewlines, France

Develop a wide range of applications for the *Mulliez Group* 

- An appointments tool for a car repair business
- An online courses platform
- A stealth product

2014 - 2016 Software Engineer @ ThredUP, San Francisco

Develop the ThredUP Operations applications running in 4 distribution centers across the USA

- 1st engineer to do a React app in 2014 and to migrate one of the app as a POC
- Develop the V2 of one of the core application
- Migrate all the remaining applications

2014 - 2012 Software Engineer Intern @ Geckoboard, UK

Develop the Geckoboard live tv dashboard application and widgets with JavaScript

- Added third-party integrations
- Developed new widgets
- Fixed and updated existing widgets

## Education

2015 Bachelor of Science in Computer Engineering, CESI, France